接下来的这首歌  稍等片刻
先来介下  绍我们的
Sunday morning rain is falling
星期天的早晨下着细雨
Steal some covers share some skin
天空被遮蔽
Clouds are shrouding us in moments unforgettable
乌云在这难忘的时刻笼罩着我们
You twist to fit the mold that I am in
你愿改变自己来适应我
But things just get so crazy living life gets hard to do
可以一切都难以控制 生活越来越糟
And I would gladly hit the road get up and go if I knew
我愿意起身上路
That someday it would lead me back to you
如果我知道有一天我会回到你身边
回到你身边
That may be all I need
我可能只需要这些
In darkness she is all I see
在黑暗中我能看到
Come and rest your bones with me
她在我身边小歇
Driving slow on Sunday morning
悠闲的星期天早晨
And I never want to leave
我永远都不要离开
My ingers trace your every  outline
手指轻拂你的酮体
Make a picture with my hands
我的手指绘下一幅地图
Back and forth we sway like branches in a storm
我们像风中的枝叶一样摇摆
Change the weather still together when it ends
四季变化 我们一直相伴
That may be all I need.Come on
我可能只需要这些
In darkness she is all I see
在黑暗中我能看到
Come and rest your bones with me
她在我身边小歇
Driving slow on Sunday morning
缓缓的星期天早晨
And I never want to leave
我永远都不要离开
You twist to fit
你愿改变自己来适应我
gets hard to do
生活越来越糟
Sunday morning rain
星期天早晨的雨
And I would get up to you baby
我会回到你身边的
it would lead me back to you
有一天我会回到你身边
Find the way get myself  back home to you
回到你身边
That may be all i need
我可能只需要这些
In darkness she is all I see
在黑暗中我能看到
Come and rest your bones with mebaby
她在我身边小歇
Driving slow
悠闲的
And I never want to leave
我永远都不要离开